Ah! The Holiday Season!
A time for celebrations,
magic,
and spending time with the people you love.
But don't forget who's
watching to make sure you're not being Naughty.
You better watch out,
You better not Skype,
You better log out,
Yeah you better not type,
The NSA is coming to town.
You're making a list,
They're checking it twice;
They're watching almost every electronic device,
The NSA is coming to town.
They see when you're sleeping,
They hear while you're awake,
They know who you call and who you write So encrypt for goodness' sake!
With Congress in the dark and a cloak-and-dagger court
We're lookin' for answers,
they're comin' up short
The NSA is coming to town.
They're making a list,
Checking it twice;
They're watching almost every electronic device,
NSA is coming to town,
The NSA is coming to town,
The NSA is coming to town.